I don't know if I'd call myself a data scientist,
我不知道该不该称自己为数据科学家,
but actually I work a lot with data scientist and also build tools for data scientists.
但实际上我和数据科学家一起工作 也为数据科学家开发工具
I work in the Watson Data and AI group.
我在沃森数据和人工智能小组工作
I'd been at this lab since 2001,
我从2001年起就在这个实验室了,
and been working in the field of data management, databases,
一直致力于数据管理 数据库,
and unstructured data with content management and now with AI.
以及内容管理非结构化数据 现在是人工智能
As a field of analytics has evolved and then the area of
随着分析学领域的发展 随之而来的是
data science is obviously becoming way more
数据科学显然正在变得
important and prominent and all the skills to go with it.
重要的 突出的 所有的技能去它
IBM the type of skills that we look for, obviously,
显然 IBM 是我们寻找的技能类型,
having a lot of data science skills and analytical skills.
拥有丰富的数据科学技能和分析技能
People that also have an understanding of some of the business,
对某些业务也有所了解的人,
and maybe some of the industries,
也许还有一些产业,
is also very helpful.
也很有帮助
So they can work with business analysts and product managers.
因此 他们可以与业务分析师和产品经理合作
The other part is not just a data science skills,
另一部分不仅仅是数据科学技能,
but it has some programming skills that help integrate into an application,
但它有一些编程技巧 可以帮助集成到应用程序中,
and even understanding the architectures of artificial intelligence and data science,
甚至理解人工智能和数据科学的架构,
and how the whole data and models all flow together.
以及整个数据和模型是如何一起流动的
So people that have combinations of those skills are really valuable.
所以那些拥有这些技能的人是非常有价值的
I think that's really a key part of this whole thing,
我觉得这是整件事的关键,
having somebody that's both knows the science,
找一个既懂科学又懂科学的人,
but also is curious and wants to apply it,
但同时也很好奇 想要应用它,
and is willing to learn the contexts of the original problem.
并且愿意学习原始问题的背景
So I'm really excited that these online courses,
所以我很高兴这些在线课程,
people can get educated,
人们可以接受教育,
and you really educate people that have been in
你真的教育了那些
traditional fields to re-learn these new skills,
重新学习这些新技能,
because these are the skills that we need now.
因为这些是我们现在需要的技能 .最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6